OMG! You're a genius! I'm freaking out! Seriously, Gojo, I'm blown away!
I'm glad that it fits you so well.
Mm-hmm. It fits perfectly.
All that's left is the wig.
Okay, but wait.
What's wrong?
Um, nothing really. The outfit's so great, but when I cosplay, I start to feel like the character.
Huh?
So, Gojo, I mean, ma-ma-master, will you please, please look? Please? Look at what I'm hiding under here.
Please, look. I want you to see.
What the hell was that?
So, do you think you could look the other way?
Thank you.
Morning.
What a messed up way to start the day. How am I supposed to talk to her now? Now that my subconscious violated us.
Look, it's Kitikawa.
Oh, Marina's such a cutie.
Hello, Kitikawa.
Hi.
I bet she's like a model or something.
For sure.
She's not even real.
I call witchcraft.
I'm guessing she's pretty popular.
Well, Dad, look at her.
Hey, I get it.
This whole thing is so surreal.
I can't believe someone like her was in my house this weekend.
Whatever.
It's fine.
I just need to stay calm.
Oh.
Hey, Gojo.
Hello.
Hi.
Good morning.
How are you?
Amazing.
Thanks to you.
You're excited to become Shizuku Town.
You totes made my day.
Um.
I'm so sorry.
Huh?
About what, weirdo?
Can you tell?
I decided to curl my hair at the bottom today.
Uh.
Um.
Yeah.
Yeah, you did.
I see it.
You see it?
I would hope so.
Right.
I'm sorry.
What you guys talking about?
I want to hang out with you two.
Kitagawa's friend.
What's her name?
Yo.
I'm Noah.
Oh.
Good morning to you, Noah.
Good morning, noob.
Oh.
Hey, uh.
Morning.
I do not know how to do this.
It's cool to see you actually talk.
Hi there.
I do.
Thanks.
Pleasure to meet you.
Sucker?
Uh, sure.
Thank you.
Maureen, is this a joke?
Hm?
This guy's obviously uncomfortable.
Maybe you should just, like, leave him alone.
Oh, he's fine.
See?
Yeah, sure.
Let's go.
We still have to get snacks before our first period starts.
Oh, crap.
You're so right.
Later.
See you around.
All right.
Hey, do you have change?
I've only got bigger.
She's not acting any differently.
No problem.
She's treating me the exact same way at school.
Am I hallucinating?
Is she going out with that loser?
Shut up.
You're right.
Can you imagine?
I don't want to.
Yo, Gojo!
Okay, so I have the best idea.
After school today, you and I should...
I'd love to, but I can't.
There's something else I have to do.
Gojo, come here.
About today.
Bathroom break?
Gojo!
Where are you?
Are you in here?
Gojo!
Come on!
There you are!
Finally!
That was a close one.
Hi, Kitagawa.
I've been looking everywhere for you.
I want to take you shopping.
I know some cute places that have what we need for the outfit.
I'm so sorry.
I'm gonna have to pass.
What?
You found me?
But how?
Seriously, you're in the middle of the sidewalk.
I used my eyes.
You've been avoiding me all day, haven't you?
You got a problem, then say so.
Don't be a coward and hide from me.
What?
You found me?
But how?
Seriously, you're in the middle of the sidewalk.
I used my eyes.
You've been avoiding me all day, haven't you?
You got a problem, then say so.
Don't be a coward and hide from me.
You're right.
Sorry.
It's just that when people see us together, they're gonna think that we, uh,
that we know each other.
You know?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Kitagawa.
If you're gonna apologize, then don't run away in the first place.
What?
You found me?
But how?
Seriously, you're in the middle of the sidewalk.
I used my eyes.
You've been avoiding me all day, haven't you?
You got a problem, then say so.
Don't be a coward and hide from me.
You're right, sorry.
It's just that when people see us together, they're gonna think that we, uh,
that we know each other, you know?
So maybe we shouldn't hang out.
At least while others are around.
Huh?
What are you even saying?
Why shouldn't people know we're friends?
Huh?
Well, um, I also heard some people in the hallway saying that we might be, you know, going out.
Seriously?
Hmm.
Well, then why don't we?
Why?
What do you mean?
Really?
Come on!
Let's go out!
Hurry up!
You're too slow!
Huh?
No, I'm not!
I just don't know where we're going!
I told you!
We're going shopping!
How cool that they have an entire cosplay session.
I know, right?
So many people are into cosplay these days, especially on Halloween.
That makes sense.
Oh, by the way, I wanted to ask.
Huh?
Could you take a look at this?
Holy shit!
I drew a multi-view design map of Shizuku-tan's costume.
We need quite a few things.
Fabric, lace, ribbons, artificial roses, shoes, a wig, fasteners, color contacts, garters and stockings.
And also...
Stop the car!
Are you saying you drew all of this?
Like, all of it?
Uh, yeah.
That is insane.
Okay, so the skirt here is pretty poofy, right?
Uh-huh.
I bet we can get the volume we need by adding a petticoat underneath.
We'll have to buy one that's ready-made, but...
Okay.
I'm down.
Also, this shoe style is pretty unique.
I'm guessing we'll need to get them from a specialty shop somewhere?
The style is called Gothic Lolita, I think.
I'll look for them.
By the way, what about the collar?
Uh, um...
Oh yeah, that.
I've honestly never made one before.
I might be able to find one at a VK shop.
I'll keep an eye out.
Okay.
Thank you.
I appreciate that.
Look.
How about that fabric?
Hmm.
Will it work?
I don't know.
Let me see.
I kinda feel like this one would work better.
Huh?
But how?
I don't see a difference.
Slippery Girls Academy is a school for upper-class girls, right?
So I would think that Shizukatan's uniform would reflect her status.
I figure we should go with fabric that's a bit thicker and heavier,
since the glossier materials tend to be cheaper.
You're so right!
Ah, but it's literally double the price of the other one.
Oh crap!
I wasn't planning on shopping today, so I'm not carrying any cash on me.
We can't get anything right now.
Don't you worry your pretty little head about that.
Mama went to the bank.
Boom.
Use whatever you need from here.
I can't do that.
It doesn't feel right.
Oh, don't be dramatic.
I've been saving up for cosplay for a while.
Yeah, but...
Take it.
Please, or I did all that work for nothing.
Okay, okay.
Yay!
Let's get to it then.
I think we managed to get everything.
Thanks for carrying all that.
Sure.
And we're off!
Next stop, Swallowtail!
I have no idea what that is.
This place is cray.
You're gonna wet your pants the moment you stand up.
You're gonna wet your pants.
I don't know what that is.
I think we managed to get everything.
Thanks for carrying all that.
Sure.
And we're off!
Next stop, Swallowtail!
I have no idea what that is.
This place is cray.
You're gonna wet your pants the moment you step in here.
It's nuts!
I can't wait.
You weren't kidding.
Told you so? It hypes you up, huh?
I love it here. Just looking around gives me a rush.
Yeah, I get that.
It really is amazing. So many different styles. In every color imaginable.
They're all so... beautiful.
Gojo!
I found it. Medium black.
Black?
Yep. This one's styled just like hers. It's perfect.
The style's great, but I think we should do this color.
Huh? That one? Why? It looks kind of purple.
Sure. But I think Shizuku-tan's character color is purple, isn't it?
I mean, her hair is black, but it looks like it has some depth to it.
Plus, a purple tint feels more her.
Oh, good call.
For such a big fan, she doesn't pay much attention to details.
I think we should go with this black violet.
Or wait, maybe the deep violet instead.
Also, the length's wrong. We need to get one that's longer.
But why?
Shizuku-tan has an asymmetrical bob, so just a medium length won't work.
If we buy it longer, we can trim it for accuracy.
Oh, yeah! I'll get it cut at my salon!
Wait, by a real stylist? That's perfect!
Bobs are super hard to cut.
I'm glad you're here.
I was planning on doing all this alone today.
What?
But every time I do that, it's a mess.
I always pick out the most inaccurate pieces.
We would have been in big trouble.
You saved me so much time.
And money, too.
Thank you.
All right, I'm gonna go buy this.
Okay.
Unbelievable.
I guess that means...
Maybe today...
I was actually useful.
Sorry for the wait.
I got some color contacts, too.
Here, I'll hold that for you.
Oh, sweet. Thanks.
One more stop to go.
She needs her garters and stockings.
Let me know if I can help you.
Hey, Kitagawa?
How much longer do you think it'll be before we go?
Not much longer.
Hey, it's just...
I don't know if I'm allowed in here.
Um, because I'm a guy.
Yeah, I know you are, Doofus.
I know you do.
I'm just worried that other customers might not be comfortable with me here.
Couples come in together all the time.
You're fine.
This is so incredibly awkward.
Hurry up, Kitagawa, please.
Gojo, check it out.
What do you think?
Doesn't this look hot?
Yikes!
I can see everything down there.
Cover up!
Actually, I was hoping to find a way to thank you for today, somehow.
Would you like something sexier?
Please!
Just let me go home!
I can't take it!
Andy's a screamer!
Everything was great!
Thanks a ton, man!
Come back soon!
Yum!
That was so good!
Agreed.
It was delicious.
Teenagers on a date.
That sure takes me back.
I miss those days.
Adulting ruins lives.
Okay, moment of truth.
What did you think of Slippery Girls?
Honestly, I haven't finished it yet.
What part are you on?
The one where he's up in front of the whole school at the morning assembly and can't stop ejaculating?
I can't even imagine that.
What in the actual hell?
I know I was panicking for him.
Poor guy just couldn't stop.
Does she think that's funny or something?
What's going on with his body?
Our future is in their sick little hands.
Terrifying.
If you want, I can take all this back to my place.
Sounds good.
I'll get the pattern drawn up for you, too.
For real?
Hell yeah!
Where's the first place I should wear it once it's complete?
Are there designated areas?
There are all kinds of events where cosplay groups get their photos taken.
Like they'll rent out amusement parks for super creative shoots.
Those who aren't as extra might go to a studio or even just cosplay at home.
I totes want to do some blingy photo booth shots, too.
Basically, you're only limited by your own creativity.
Fascinating.
Oh, and of course, you can always post your favorites to your social meets.
What?
You put those photos on the internet?
Uh, duh.
Why not?
Look.
That's amazing.
I can't tell if she got that done at a studio.
I love the details.
Do you think she crafted her own props?
She probably bought them.
Oh, look at this one!
Her name is Juju.
Isn't she offensively cute?
I'm basically obsessed with her.
She cosplays a lot of younger anime characters, like magical girls and stuff.
She's gorgeous, and the quality of her costumes and photos are sick!
That's why she's got like a gazillion followers.
Apparently, she doesn't go to events, so she's like this eternal mystery.
But I'm pretty sure she's a total pro.
Wow.
She looks really young, though.
How old do you think she is?
Hmm.
She might be in middle school, or at the end of grade school.
Huh?
Oh my gosh, look!
She's cosplaying pre-transformation Shion Akairo from Flower Princess Blaze!
Her outfit is perfect!
She's so freaking cute!
I could literally throw up and die!
There's a theme.
Black hair.
It's a thing for you.
And what about you, Kettle?
Oh, right.
Good point there.
Guess we're the same.
You gotta see this!
They're so pretty!
Wow, this one's effing gorgeous!
I swear girls who cosplay guys are my jam!
Damn!
Look how hot this one is!
Why are you mute all of a sudden?
Are you immune to beauty or something?
What?
No, I swear.
Nothing like that.
Then what is it?
Well, um...
It just made me think of something else from my childhood.
I don't have any siblings.
So the first time I ever saw a doll was on the shelf at my grandpa's store.
Huh?
I couldn't take my eyes off of her.
I thought to myself, how can something so beautiful exist in this world?
It was like she reached in and stole my heart.
There, in that moment, I first understood what the word beautiful meant.
Nothing else could describe her.
And no other word since then could be used to define things that are the most precious to me.
So I don't say beautiful or pretty, unless it comes from the heart.
Okay, but like, Hina dolls are all painted to look super gorgeous, right?
Gojo, you're a total face guy.
I hope I didn't say something wrong.
I'm sorry.
I have a hard time giving compliments.
I mean, it's not like I'm denying that those people look good, but...
Dude, if that's your coat or whatever, it's totally fine to own it.
Hey, it's okay not to compromise on stuff.
I've got some things I'm pretty hardcore about, too.
Like boob bags, for instance?
Yep.
Oh, baby!
I gotta get that in my mouth!
It looks so good!
You sure you don't want me to get you on Gojo?
Because I'll totes cover you.
I'm sure.
Thanks, though.
Okay, be right back!
Huh?
How can she eat anything after we just had all that ramen?
Damn, I went on a spending binge today.
I'll have to add more hours at work.
Wait!
I forgot to pay you back for the ramen.
What?
I told you that was on me.
I stole your whole day.
If you're sure.
I promise it's fine.
It's just that...
It made me really happy.
It's not very often that someone actually plays a game I recommend, you know?
Most people will say,
Yeah, that seems fun.
And then awkwardly change the subject.
To be completely honest,
I didn't think you'd be the type to get into a game like Slippery Girls.
My bad.
I mean,
you're the one who drew her outfit perfectly,
right down to the very last detail.
It's hard to admit,
but you're more of an expert on it than me.
And, um,
I have a point.
I appreciate you.
Okay?
Thank you, Gojo.
Besides,
since I can't really sew,
the only way I can help is by emptying my wallet.
Right?
No,
that's not true.
Anyway,
this meat roll is giving me life right now.
Here,
have a bite.
It'll blow your mind.
Open.
Here.
No,
that's an indirect kiss.
Oh, no.
I really couldn't eat another bite.
You've treated me to more than enough today.
I'm super stuffed.
Okay.
Please,
don't be upset.
I'm not,
but you're missing out.
Oh,
no.
Hmm?
Oh, no.
You'll probably think I'm a total pig,
don't you?
Huh.
No,
not at all.
Liar!
Look,
I'm not gonna get fat for eating like this,
okay?
Quit staring at me with that tone of voice.
I'm fine!
Of course you're fine.
I wasn't judging you.
I swear.
My body needs carbs,
okay?
It's not my fault.
It's science!
Oh, yeah.
I hear you.
Whatever.
I'm not eating anything until the event.
I promise I'll still be able to fit into my cosplay.
You have to eat.
But when does this event take place?
Hmm?
Hmm.
Let's see.
Oh, here it is.
Looks like in exactly two weeks.
Oh, crap.
Sorry!
I gotta go or I'll miss my train!
Thanks for everything today!
See you later, Kojo!
Wait.
What?
Who?
How?
The events in two weeks?
Okay.
What?
The baddest
Of course try to?
Welcome back!
What?
Maybe we are catching various things.
We're not touching.
Let's go.
I love you
Your estate who's been so shamed
in a moment that I've seen some των
Oh, I don't know what it was
You can't watch that
But now, it's a secret
In sync with beauty
It's that smallest heart
Xeme
?
Next time.